we're going to add tomatoes we're gonna
do jalapeno put a little cilantro in
there all I taste is jalapeno
tomato and cilantro internet product
reviews saving people all across the
world from buying useless products every
single day at least uh sometimes now I
say sometimes because While most
reviewers have their fellow consumer in
mind some people will just say anything
as long as it benefits them and today we
will be looking at just that with Jack's
calfani a bit of a different kind of
Jack video we're not really going to be
watching him cook today kind of but
mainly we're here for his review on the
Magic Bullet a review so biased that I
actually feel kind of dirty calling it a
review so you might be thinking okay
August what could really be so bad about
a product review about something bought
off the television you know you might be
expecting a review of an as seen on TV
product to not be very good and sure
I'll give you that one but the reason
this review turns out bad is for all of
the wrong reasons I'm not joking when I
tell you that every single negative
thing that Jack has to say about the
Magic Bullet has absolutely nothing to
do with the magic bullet itself the man
and literally blames his cooking skills
on a TV blender think I'm joking well
you're about to see let's begin now
please subscribe welcome to the show
Jack scalfani here and you're cooking
with Jack and this is the episode you've
been waiting for you've been asking or
should I say you've been nagging uh not
even 10 seconds in and there's the Jack
I know and love constantly berating his
audience for asking for more content
what a guy it's the most requested
product review show it's called the
Magic Bullet so we're going to take a
look at that in a moment but first
there's something
all right before we do The Omelette
let's take a quick look at the
infomercial and see how they made the
omelette
[Music]
now that you've seen how they did it
let's grab it and make our own
what's really cool about this is
this has little legs so it doesn't fall
over while you're trying to put your
eggs in there two eggs right one tomato
thing of cheese thing of ham
and let's put in
a little bit of onion it's all there
just like the video cool let's see if it
does exactly like she did okay
there's your breakfast right there so
I'm gonna put it on
okay and she did it for three two counts
of three so we're gonna go one two three
one two three
and that's what she did all right so so
far nothing bad pretty fair review just
doing what the infomercial did and
that's fair if it was shown on the
commercial it should be able to do it
when you buy it and I know you guys
couldn't see it but he did follow what
the infomercial did pretty closely
that's not really the issue here that's
to follow here's what I want to show you
okay this isn't even done cooking inside
yet this has been hard to cook I know
I'm burning the bottom of this already
so I'm taking it out now but I mean it's
not even fully cooked on the inside
doesn't cook well
so I'm going to roll this out
I guarantee we've already burnt the
outside
and look it's runny on the inside
and burnt on the outside look at that
look at that it doesn't even cook well
unbelievable that's too bad because it
Blended really well
all right I consider that a fail I don't
like that at all nope you heard that
right jack admits that The Omelette
mixture Blended fine but it didn't cook
right he is blaming his inability to
cook an omelette on the blender Jack
that's not burnt that's how cooked egg
looks like now look it would be one
thing if he said it didn't blend right
or if it wasn't mixed up enough but he
said that it Blended really well so
what's the excuse how is this being
blamed on the Magic Bullet Jack you
cooked the omelet in a pan not the
blender
we're going to add tomatoes thing of
garlic tada
little bit onions
in fact I'll I'll help it along I'm
going to break this in half there's no
no complaining that I use too big of a
size of onion
we're gonna do jalapeno
and we're gonna do a little bit of
break off some of this cilantro put a
little cilantro in there okay
now I expect this one to pass well I
wouldn't Jack because you're not using
the same ingredients that the
infomercial is you're using like half
the amount of tomatoes when making salsa
so yeah I don't see this one working out
either but not because of the bullets is
going to be an incredible salsa if this
works that might be worth it for me
here we go and he did it for three
seconds here we go
one
two
three and
there it is
hmm
looked like his does it
exact same ingredients all right take a
look
wow
why doesn't that look the same I don't
get it I use the exact same stuff she
did well Jack maybe because once again
you only used half the amount of
tomatoes and you did it for a
considerably shorter amount of time than
they did on the infomercial I think he
was kind of Jaded by the Almond at this
point and he was like trying to make the
product look bad I know I'm sounding
like a Magic Bullet brand ambassador or
something but I really just don't like
to see things reviewed unfairly if
you're gonna make a product review do it
right don't get mad because you messed
up an omelet and then try to make the
product look bad intentionally
and look or he did really look there's
even garlic in there that's not even
broken up
let's see what that is before I go
tasting this this looks nasty we're
going to show you what it looks like
come on look at that
doesn't even look like
it didn't even mix it well all right so
let me try this out see what it tastes
like
smells good looks nasty I mean does it
really look nasty it just looks like a
chunky salsa if anything really I as
well like more liquidy Salsas but like
this does not look nasty I don't think
it looks like exactly what it is
oh man
whew
okay
wasn't ready for that
it tastes nasty all it takes is jalapeno
tomato and cilantro oh my God Jack I I
wonder why why would you possibly taste
jalapeno tomato and cilantro in a salsa
that you made out of jalapeno tomato and
cilantro oh my goodness somebody please
get this in front of a team of
scientists I mean what a joke of a
review yeah guys uh this waffle maker
really isn't for me it turned my batter
into something that really looked like a
waffle and personally more of a pancake
guy the garlic is in the chunk here
didn't even make it throughout the whole
salsa this is a fail this is just nasty
looking I'm starting to think that Jag
may have never seen a salsa before
garlic worked we're just going for it
stick some onion in there
break off the root part of it
put it right in there and see what it
does three
[Music]
oh
don't even
there we go
hold on a minute
I don't know what happened but let's
take a look
that was weird
okay see that yeah that looks good
but it's not
look at this
can't even cut up an onion Jack you were
literally taking it off of the blender
halfway through every quarter second
blend you did like I have a pretty nice
food processor that I use quite often
and even it takes a good amount of time
to cut up something like onion I went
and watched the infomercial and it did
not claim to be able to cut up an onion
in less than one second I mean what are
your expectations for a blender it's a
blender
okay last test here we go
we're gonna do cheese take cheese right
here okay I'm putting one in there one
in there I'm not cutting anything up
anymore throw in a piece of jalapeno
we're gonna hit that
I can't even get it to chop up the other
cheese
come on
[Music]
and I don't like the fact that as soon
as you touch it it locks itself really
touchy
ah
I'm totally frustrated look at this mess
all right look you can't even cut the
cheese up
you know I'm not even gonna do it I'm
not even gonna make this all right so I
had absolutely no idea what he was
trying to accomplish here so I just went
through the 30 minute infomercial once
more and apparently he was trying to
recreate a section where you'd like chop
up some cheese and jalapeno to just make
the cheese easier to melt I don't think
it was ever supposed to be like it
turned into cheese powder also I read a
lot of the comments on Jack's video and
apparently he's not using the magic of
bullet right he never reads the
instructions of the products he's
reviewing for whatever reason so he
normally uses them wrong and then gets
angry about it so yeah the reason it's
not blending correctly and it like keeps
locking up and coming off is because he
doesn't have it attached properly so
yeah super review Jack wow that's all I
can say I've never been so frustrated on
an episode as I am today that is the
biggest piece of garbage the Magic
Bullet don't don't even look at it are
you looking at it nope
it gets no more attention that's it no
more don't buy it I'm not buying it in
fact I'm giving this one back to my dad
I'm glad I stole it from him because I
don't even want that I would have been
upset I spent 60 bucks on that and don't
get me started on shipping that's a
whole another topic we will talk about
that in another episode all right so I'm
not like here to defend the Magic Bullet
I'm sure it's not the greatest blender
or food processor on Earth but this kind
of video is just not fair for anybody to
do this video got a lot of views like
over a million views and that's a bunch
of people seeing somebody with quote
first-hand experience with a product
who's saying it's terrible and you
should never buy it and it's the worst
thing ever when they're not even using
it properly and most of the things that
went wrong for them were their own fault
look I'm sure any infomercial product
from the 2000s is not exactly the
Pinnacle of quality but if your main
complaints or that you didn't cook an
egg right and that you couldn't figure
out how to make salsa don't blame it on
the blender well guys what do you think
was Jack out of line with this review or
was the Magic Bullet actually plotting
against his omelet this video was
weirdly nostalgic for me because I
remember seeing these infomercials all
the time personally I always wanted that
Slushy Magic thing does anybody else
remember that 2000's television maybe
good times if you enjoyed this video
please leave a like and walk on over to
that subscribe button and touch it it's
free it won't cost you anything but for
now that's all I have for you today bye
[Music]
subscribe